(Amy:)What's going on here?
(Sheldon:)You expressed an interest
in having people over,
(Sheldon:)and I feel
I dismissed it too quickly.
(Sheldon:)So, I took matters
(Sheldon:)into my own hands,
and I arranged a brunch.
(Amy:)Well, that's so nice.
(Amy:)Who's coming?
(Sheldon:)Oh, uh, Stuart,
Bert from the geology lab,
(Sheldon:)and Mrs. Petrescu
from downstairs.
(Amy:)You mean the Romanian lady
on the second floor?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
Oh, fun story:
(Sheldon:)she grew up with ten siblings.
(Sheldon:)Or possibly penguins.
Her English is atrocious.
(Amy:)That's an odd mix of people.
(Sheldon:)Well, for our first time
hosting,
(Sheldon:)I thought it would be wise
to conduct a trial run.
(Amy:)You know,
like how I practiced
(Sheldon:)for that Halloween haunted house
(Sheldon:)by going into the bathroom
at the bus station.
(Amy:)You never went
into that haunted house.
(Sheldon:)You never saw what jumped out
at me at the bus station.
(Amy:)Well, thank you, Sheldon.
(Amy:)This is a fun surprise.